option.  Finishing off this
graphics library a bit, for example
by putting the legend, okay?, in each
of the countries, that is, okay, when I
hover the mouse over it, it tells me the value,
which is super cool, but
let's see,
uh, just a moment.
Okay, perfect.  Now
I would like.
to add static legends
to P slices
eh
and independently
to eh tool tips.
I mean, I like toolti tipps,
okay?  But I
also want to add a series of
legends so that at least
this makes a little sense here.  By the way, I
should also include the titles of
the graphs, that is, what does
each graph represent?  Well, let's
do it now.
And the idea is a bit like that, isn't it?  The idea
is what I'm telling you, that the issue is not
this, it's a bit like what we were
talking about before in
multimedia programming.  The idea isn't to make a
video game, it's to make a
video game engine, okay?  It's the same here.  The
idea is not to make a graph, but to make
a library of graphs.  It's about working on
designing components, because you
know Friday is coming and
we're going to need components in
business management systems.  And if we're going to
start creating reports, if
we're going to start creating charts,
we're going to need those components
ready to be able to use them.  Well,
the idea is a bit like this, right?  Today,
in interfaces, we're creating graphics,
in data mining, we're creating
data components, and all of this seems
pointless. Then,
I insist, business management systems will come,
and in business management systems
, just as we saw
last week, it will be very useful for us to have
developed those components so we can
use them.  Okay, so I'll come here for
a moment.
This over here.  This over here.
Okay, just a second.  I was doing this
over here.
Let's see.
Okay, so we have this over here.
Let's go to 020 legends in the
slices,
the parts,
okay?  And from here
we'll see it.  Legends in the parts.
Okay.  Okay.  Correct.  Good.  It is
a bit overprinted, but well, it
is basically expected.  And
then the tool tip, okay?  Then we
can make the text
smaller or customizable or who
knows, okay?  Or whatever
we want.  Okay, this over here, this over
here.  And now, as I was saying, I think
I would add one more thing, which is a
title, okay?  Because of course, what
exactly does this correspond to would be
interesting, it
would be interesting
if I now came here 021,
title of the graph
and for example label.  Ah, no.  Uh,
data.  Wait.
Data because this is a label.  Okay.
Okay.
Oh, which would be necessary for me.  It doesn't
matter because we'll be able to do it
without any problem,
but
I would need it.
Well, you know what?  Not really,
not really, not really, because the
title
is countries, cities,
programming languages.  Routes,
okay?  Which means
countries,
cities,
programming languages
and fruits.
Okay?  So now what I want
is to modify this and with this we are already
focusing on the end of the class, but
calmly.  Eh, please
eh, let's see
chart title
ability
to eh
to the software.
Okay.
Of course, from here, as you can
imagine,
we can create as many graphs as
necessary.  I mean, if while
this is cooking, if I come
here and say, well, chart eh types,
well, look, okay?  See if there is anything
here to do, from the basics,
where today, for example, in this class
we have done the foot and the bar to
columns, lines, which we could have also
done in a simple way, donuts,
which is a foot, but with a circle in
the middle, Babel charge, radar or
spider web,
scatter, comparison tables, okay?
Googes that I love, okay?  I
love those and we can do them in a very
simple way and then obviously
more advanced graphics.
So the idea of ​​today's class,
as I said, is to give you a little bit of an
idea that we can't just make one or
two or three different types of graphs,
but that we can make as many as we
want.
Let's wait a moment for this to end.
Okay.
and 022 and title of the graph.
And now we come here
and try.
And okay, for example, that's great.   An
important note is that from the
point of view of interaction with
artificial intelligence, well, there is
one, that is, the idea, as you can see, is that we
always begin to develop
the base so that once
we have developed the base and once
we have pointed out where the
project is going, we can tell the AI,
"Okay, now make variations, make
modifications."
A slightly more advanced level is to
give him
samples of how we program and
say, "Develop it for me, but
do it my way."  Okay?  So that?
So that everything we
do,
obviously, we can understand it and we
can modify it and, ultimately, we don't
feel like
we programmed it, which doesn't matter.   I
mean, obviously the highest part
, the most complete part has been
done by Chat GPT, there's no problem
with that, but we can then
get our hands on the code
and Chat GPT doesn't do something that's
super cool, but then when we put it in
the code we say, "Wow, what is this,
okay? Or yeah, I recognize what it is, but
this style is not my style, so it's
hard for me to get used to this style, okay?
But anyway, so, that's all for today
because of what's going on, okay? And
besides, as I'm telling you, the power went out in
the neighborhood, so I think
we're 10 minutes away from the
power going out here in the building. So
we'll continue on Thursday, you know, with
data access and
with processes and services and then,
as you know, we'll continue on Friday
with the intermodular project and with uh
business management systems. Uh,
you know, you know what I was saying
before, that we'll hit the ground running,  the
starting gun for,
okay? The evaluation, so,
from here on you know that by
clicking here, right? Right here, no,
where, okay? By clicking here,
you will find the subjects you
are enrolled in and you will find
suggested exercises, so then you
can start developing. If you
have any questions, of
course, ask me, but come on, I
mean, don't worry, just by
following the evaluation rubric you will see
that the first exercise will be difficult, but do
n't worry because from there the
next and the next and the next
exercise you will see that they are always the same
because the rubric is the same and I'm
telling you, I mean, the idea is uh that you include
a bit of literature, but that by including
literature it serves to demonstrate that you
know about the subject and then
obviously, well, we will talk
in a few weeks, just like
last year, do you remember how to convert what you
are doing into
social media posts for  You guys? I mean, you
can turn your own
practices into your own portfolio, so you can
sell your
companies, let's say, okay? So, well,
we'll continue. We'll continue on Thursday and
that's it. I'll upload the videos later, and if
you need anything else, just
let me know, okay?
Okay, guys, it's up
to you now. M.